realtybargains.com 2011-10-18

# Foreclosures, Pre-Foreclosures , FSBO and Real Estate Owned properties nation wide

## Privacy policy

Personal Information - Realty Bargains will collect certain personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") from you, including all information requested during the registration process and information you enter in connection with services you request and searches you conduct. Personal Information may include, among other information, your name, postal address, email address, date of birth, household income, and real estate searches/interests.

Realty Bargains may use your Personal Information (i) to provide you with access to the Website and its services; (ii) to provide you with or assist with any services or goods you request; (iii) to operate, maintain and improve the Website and its services; and (iv) to ensure your compliance with the Terms and Conditions of Use of the Website.

Use of Personal Information by Affiliates - In addition to the foregoing uses, Realty Bargains may share Personal Information with affiliates who provide services in connection with the Website (as defined in the Terms and Conditions), including among others, real estate brokers and agents, mortgage brokers, mortgage lenders, home inspectors and real estate attorneys. These affiliates may contact you in connection with the services they offer.

Credit Card and Banking Information - In connection with your registration and use of the Website, you may provide Realty Bargains with credit card and/or bank account information. Realty Bargains will use this information solely for the purposes of collecting fees you authorize. Realty Bargains will not share your credit card and banking information with third parties except (i)for the purposes of processing the fees you have authorized and (ii)for any other purpose you authorize.

Aggregate Information - Realty Bargains may use non-personally identifiable information ("Aggregate Information") to improve the Website and users experiences. Realty Bargains may also share Aggregate Information with third parties, including among others advertisers and prospective advertisers on the Website.

Maintenance of Information - Realty Bargains will make its best efforts to maintain all user information securely. You agree to release and hold harmless Realty Bargains for any damages arising out of any failure of such efforts.

Provision of Information Pursuant to Law - Without limiting any of the preceding, Realty Bargains may provide to third parties pursuant to court order, subpoena or other legal process any information you provide to it and any information Realty Bargains collects.

Cookies - Realty Bargains may store information on your computer (often called "cookies") to facilitate your use of the Website and to track your usage of the Website.

Changes to This Privacy Policy - Realty Bargains may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. Notification regarding such changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on the Website.

Effective Date - This Privacy Policy is effective September 1, 2006.
